From
Mr. Omar Boado
Brgy. Ipilan, Tayabas City
Quezon Province

To Dra. Liwanag Administrator Tayabas Community Hospital, Inc

Dear Madam,

I, Omar, Writing this letter to introduce myself to you. I am applying for the job as System Support(System Maintenance and Server Maintenance), Programmer, Web Designer in your esteemed institution. I have just cleared my Bachelor Degree in Information Technology from Saint Louis College, La Union Branch. I have 5 years Experience in IT industry. This includes system supports and programming.

The job shall help me get the foundation for the career which I have been longing for, I am skilled in communication, and can adapt to the given context within no time. I am capable of coping with any amount of work pressure and still can deliver the desired results.

My resume have been enclosed along with this letter. I looked forward for the meeting and association with your esteemed company.

Yours faithfully, Omar Boado

### Omar Boado

### Senior Programmer/ Senior Software Engineer

Innovative, forward-thinking executive offering over 5 years of success in various leadership roles in the areas of Information Technology consulting, customer support, pre-sales engineering, and global business development. Expert in strategic and tactical planning, and client relationship management (CRM).



omar.boado.09121989@gmail.com 🔀

+63909 635 8335

San Fernando City La Union, Philippines Q

### SKILLS

Programming

Communication

**Logical Thinking** 

#### **LANGUAGES**

Tagalog, Ilokano, English
Professional Working Proficiency

# WORK EXPERIENCE IT Staff

Yamaha Wheeltek Corp

02/2017 - 07/2017

Maintains Computers, Printers, Internet Connection and System data/s

### Senior HRIS Programmer

Software Engineer, Kaiser Dela Cruz Consulting Inc. - MEDSYS. San Fernando City, La Union

08/2017 - Present

A company that develops HIS (hospital Information System) and HRIS (Human Resource Information System)

#### Achievements/Tasks

- Responsible for design, development, maintenance, testing, and evaluation of HRIS Module (Human Resource Information System) that includes
   Personnel, Biometrics, Timekeeping and Payroll Module.
- Performed production system software installations and gathering software requirements from clients(Hospitals and other bussiness establishments) and end users.
- Maintain existing Crystal Reports and rewrites/modifies according to clients format.
- Developed and Optimized Stored Procedures and Functions using T-SQL.
- Modify and customize commercial programs for internal needs.
- Can maintain, fix/troubleshoot Hardwares/Computers.
- Trained End user/s on how to use the Medsys System
- Implement HRIS (Human Resource Information System)
   Actual and Remote Impelementation, ff client: CHDG at
   La trinidad Benguet SLU Hospital in Baguio, Sacred
   Hospital in Angeles Pampanga, NKTI in Quezon City, Ace
   Hospital in Dumaguete, Rosario Hospital in Guagua
   Pampanga, VRP Hospital in Mandaluyong City, and TCHI
   in Tayabas Quezon)

#### **EDUCATION**

## Batchelor of Science in Information Technology

Saint Louis College

San Fernando City La Union

Course

Information Technology

Saint Louis High school - Virac Virac, Itogon Benguet

Virac Itogon Benguet

06/2012 - 04/2016